I've...
turned into a man?
I wish to bring the General
some late-night snacks.
Please let me through.
Well...
Are you bribing me
or taking advantage of me?
Isn't this the one from last time?
He is the second male lead, Ning Yuanci.
General, have a cup of wine
to warm yourself up.
General,
spare my life!
Wait, what did she do to you?
Didn't I tell you that
no woman
is allowed near my courtyard?
You're a total player outside.
Stop pretending to be a saint.
Since the character bio
says I'm a loyal guard,
it never hurts to suck up to the boss,
right?
I was worried you'd get hungry
while bathing,
so I had her bring you a snack.
I promise
I won't give these
seductive women
another chance to tempt you.
Get my clothes.
This feel...
Sorry,
I didn't mean to.
I'm even playing a man,
and he's still disgusted.
It's either bed scenes or nude scenes.
Do they have any other tricks?
That sword.
He's the one
who silenced me last time.
What are you staring at?
Go get the clothes.
I'll go get the clothes for you.
Why are you acting so weird today?
What do you have to report?
N-N-Nothing.
He really is the ruthless second male lead
who kills without blinking.
What was his storyline again?
I only remember the beginning
of the synopsis,
which seemed to say
that the miserable Xue Ruowan
was forced to marry Ning Yuanci.
General,
are you going to marry Xue Ruowan,
the daughter of the Duke of Ying?
The wedding is tomorrow.
What do you think?
The wedding is tomorrow?
What if she refuses to marry you?
If she refuses,
there is only one way out for her: death.
She dies if she doesn't marry you?
What kind of gangster logic is that?
Could Xue Ruowan's poisoning
have something to do with him too?
Xue Shiyan
thinks the Emperor's bestowed marriage
is a test of his loyalty.
In fact,
I want the Xue family
to pay the price in blood.
Bro,
how am I supposed to respond to that?
I haven't even read Mo Xiang's script.
Let's go.
Come with me to the Duke's Residence.
We're bringing them a grand gift.
What grand gift?
This is the wedding dress
bestowed by His Majesty.
Only this
is worthy of my Wan'er.
A second male lead
who changes faces so easily
and is clearly destined to turn evil.
Wan'er lost her mother at a young age
and has always been frail and sickly.
I hope the General
will treat her well.
As long as she
marries me,
I will naturally treat her well.
Xiaolan,
Deliver the wedding dress
to the Eldest Lady's room.
Yes.
Last time, Lan delivered the wedding dress
and got killed by an assassin.
Xue Ruowan was also poisoned to death.
Is the plot going to repeat itself?
I have carefully selected
this seasonal tea.
Please enjoy it, General Ning.
Wait.
How can just drinking tea be enough?
Why don't you
just stay for dinner,
General?
I need to buy more time
to save Xue Ruowan.
Let me deliver it for you.
Go do something else.
How can a grown man
like you just walk into
the young lady's room?
Xue Ruowan's poisoning
and Xiaolan's murder
might all be tied to Ning Yuanci.
I've been reborn,
so of course I have to stop
the villain from causing trouble.
Girl,
I'm trying to save your life.
How can you not tell good from bad?
Who's your sister?
If you keep doing this, I'll scream.
Miss Xue.
Thank goodness.
Sorry, sister.
Passing out here
is better than getting stabbed to death.
Sorry, I'm so sorry.
Who are you?
None of your business.
This medicine is poisoned.
Don't drink it if you want to live.
Lan,
I'm here to save you.
The one who wants to kill you
is Ning Yuanci.
Don't scream.
Brother Ning,
you said you wouldn't marry her,
right?
You called me here
just to say this?
Brother Ning,
you belong only to me.
You are mine.
A woman transmigrating into a man's body
and inheriting superb martial arts?
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Again?
Go away!
Run!
You again?
Help!
Assassin!
Help! Louder!
Help!
Assassin!
Just a petty thief.
Cui Hu,
take him down now.
So you're not the assassin?
No!
Watch out!
Cui Hu!
Am I...
Failed again.
So Ning Yuanci wasn't the assassin.
Then who exactly
wants to kill Xue Ruowan?
Actor Xia Yimo,
your plot mission has failed again.
Are you ready
to enter the next role?
Don't you have any
slightly higher-level roles?
Marginal roles like this
are destined to be cannon fodder.
What kind of role
do you want to play?
Can I choose?
Roles are randomized by the system.
I can't give you spoilers.
Then why did you ask?
It's never a bad thing
to have expectations for your future.
After all, you only have three chances
left to play.
Then...
What happens
if I use up all five chances
and the mission still fails?
You will be trapped here forever.
What?
I am willing to be a vegetarian for life,
praying to play
a noble,
highly skilled,
and beautiful woman
in the Mo Xiang script.
A choice that changes destiny.
In just a moment.
Good luck.
How dare you ruin our Second Miss's plans.
Beat her up!
Stop!
I'd like to see who dares to hit her.
Damn it!
I actually drew the role of a noble,
cunning,
and beautiful wicked stepmother.
Is this the character I get
for being a vegetarian my whole life?
Since she refuses to accept her fate,
let me teach her a good lesson.
This...